练习 1-9：名词和代词语调。第一栏重读名词。
Exercise 1-9, Noun and Pronoun Intonation. In the first column, stress the nouns. In
第二栏重读动词；在底部填写你自己的例子。
the second column, stress the verb. Fill in your own examples at the bottom. One,
Bob sees Betty. He sees her. Two, Betty knows Bob. She knows him. Three, Ann and
Ed call the kids. They call them. 4. Jan sells some apples. She sells some. 5. Gene
sells cars. She sells them. 6. Bill and I fix the bikes. We fix them. 7. Carl hears
Bob and me. He hears us. eight dogs eat bones they eat them nine the girls have a
choice they have one ten the kids like the candy they like it 11 the boys need some
help they need 12. Ellen should call her sister. She should call someone. 13. The
murderer killed the plumber. He killed a man. 14. The tourists went shopping. They
bought stuff.